hello I was not gonna do a video today
because it's Sunday and I'm on vacation
but the bus ride up here I got the next
leap
the next thing to integrate into a
global cooperative that moves it forward
and it's always so energizing I wanted
to share it right away whenever I get
the next thing it's so funny because it
clicks so much into place and become so
obvious that I'm like well I didn't I
incorporate this when I first kind of
had the e clean months and months ago
but it's not because it wouldn't have
been ready for those until I have the
World Cafe hope cafe idea of like that's
our first project this would would have
been too daunting so the next leap is
instead of concentrating on all of
humanity and let's solve all the
humanities problems which I get is a
little overwhelming
people instead I'm going to create the
social media platform we are going to
create the social media platform that's
designed for and with people with
disabilities to come together and talk
about what's not working in society for
them and then create the tools to make
it work which means the hope cafe our
version of the World Cafe that is
designed to bring people together and
have a real time conversation needs to
be accessible to people with all the
kinds of disabilities physical the
physical kinds all the mental clients
all the emotional kinds we have to meet
people where they are even more so with
this and
so much clicks into place with this eye
I can't even get it all all in a five
minute video but part of what this does
we're gonna use society's ableism
against them they're gonna let us fly
under the radar creating the tech
cooperative that Google and Facebook can
shut down it's like because we're crated
on Google and Facebook using their their
tools it's it's a little weird it's hard
to kind of like uh under not power I
don't know you're saying the disability
union hey we're a bunch of people with
disabilities getting together and
solving our own problems flies under the
radar for a much longer time and that is
what we are going to create and the
people who I'm staying with are now back
so I am going to cut this short but I
wanted to come on today and share that
little piece we are going to start a
disability union which is still the
global tech cooperative we're still
concentrating on technology it's going
to be the platforms to connect us to
give us community to give us information
we need to have access to and it's going
to have our board of directors everyone
on our board of directors is going to
have a disability self disclosed
I identify as somebody with a disability
disability hopefully they're able to
explain what that is but if they're not
because that's not who they are that's
fine too as part of what you offer as
someone with a disability is that lived
experience and it gives you something
mature to contribute to the world
which is why all of this just clicks
into place it's like the population we
need to start with because this isn't
top-down this isn't people giving
charity to us this is us co-creating
solutions what do you need what do I
need let's create it together how do we
all eat more cheaply how do you use your
power your brainpower to help me how to
use your emotional power to help me and
vice versa
how do we offset spoons and energy and
time and money so that we can help it's
already a disadvantaged community people
who have disabilities make less money so
we need to honor that how do we create
this when people people with less money
well when we're saving people $500 a
month
painting it costing them $10 a month is
it okay and those of us who have the
ability to pay $10 a month can offset
people who can't
maybe I pay $10 a month it'd bring
somebody else on board as well but now I
need to find the people I need to find
the people where where's the disability
community just like disabled Twitter
make sure there's disabled Facebook
stabled Instagram finding a way to have
that to bring people in for an actual
conversation and creating now I want to
create the hope cafe to start with like
just the first beta like with everyone
I'm like everyone put in money with this
one I'm like do I had money can I just
make this myself how much does it cost
because I really want to have the tool
to get people to the conversation this
is gonna be my obsession for the next
few
welcome to my special-interest save it
the world alright I will see you all
tomorrow or not because this is my video
and I get one day of not Toro or the
next day and you time please like and
subscribe
better world on its way and our
neurodiversity and physical diversity is
gonna bring it to you
take care